[
    {
        "question": "What does the key management in a wireless sensor network involve?",
        "answers": [
            "Generation and distribution of the keys.",
            "Storage and periodic renewal of the keys.",
            "All of the above."
        ],
        "correct": "All of the above."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Q-Composite key management scheme add on top of the classic Random Key Pre-distribution one?",
        "answers": [
            "It requires that any set of Q nodes is fully connected.",
            "It requires that two nodes share at least Q keys in orded to communicate.",
            "It does not build on the classic scheme."
        ],
        "correct": "It requires that two nodes share at least Q keys in order to communicate."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are path-keys?",
        "answers": [
            "They are keys used in intermediate nodes to connect sensors that did not share any keys directly in the discovery phase.",
            "They are keys used in recent research that implements public key criptography in wireless sensor networks."
            "They are pairs of keys distributed to the nodes that are still not connected after the shared-key discovery phase.",
        ],
        "correct": "They are keys used in intermediate nodes to connect sensors that did not share any keys directly in the discovery phase."
    },

    {
        "question": "Which layer is responsible for routing from the node to the base station?",
        "answers": [
            "Physical layer.",
            "Network layer.",
            "Link layer."
        ],
        "correct": "Network layer."
    },
    {
        "question": "How can jamming attacks be dealt with?",
        "answers": [
            "By changing the frequency at which the node send message.",
            "By making the node sleep.",
            "Either of the above."
        ],
        "correct": "Either of the above."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Sybil attack?",
        "answers": [
            "It refers to a node continuously being requested messages and being send data to.",
            "It refers to the attacker faking multiple identities.",
            "It refers to stealing information by “listening” to the message transmitted."
        ],
        "correct": "It refers to the attacker faking multiple identities."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of IDS should be used if overhead communication is to be avoided?",
        "answers": [
            "An IDS deployed on the nodes.",
            "An IDS deployed on cluster heads.",
            "An IDS deployed on the base station."
        ],
        "correct": "An IDS deployed on the nodes."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which layer is responsible for deciding at which frequency the node must transmit the message?",
        "answers": [
            "Physical layer.",
            "Link layer.",
            "Network layer."
        ],
        "correct": "Physical layer."
    },
    {
        "question": "There are two kinds of memory in a node; to which one is the RAM classified?",
        "answers": [
            "Internal.",
            "External.",
            "Both."
        ],
        "correct": "Internal."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary downside of using anomaly detection in an IDS?",
        "answers": [
            "The high rate of false alarms.",
            "Making the system vulnerable to unknown attacks.",
            "It can not detect attacks that do not violate the protocol specifications."
        ],
        "correct": "The high rate of false alarms."
    }
]